>> Jem Young: 现在我简单介绍如何安装 Redis ，以防你
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Now I'll briefly talk about
how to install Redis just in case you
想去
want to.
我们不需要因为我们今天就不能用它了
We don't have to because
we're not gonna use it today.
但是，在将来如果需要安装它，请安装重新安装服务器。
But just in the future if you need to
install it, sudo apt install redis-server.
我们要修改下一个
We're gonna modify the redis.conf,
我们要把监督线修改为 systemd
we're gonna modify
the supervised line to systemd.
所以我们要做的就是把它添加到系统守护程序中
So what we're doing is we're
adding it to the system daemon, so
系统会在系统重新启动时始终处于联机状态。
that it will always come online
when the system restarts.
还记得昨天有人问服务，什么是服务，有人做了。
Remember yesterday someone asked about
services, what are services, someone did.
当我们谈到服务的时候我说 sudo nginx 服务
When we talked about services,
when I say sudo nginx service,
等等，使用 systemctl，这是服务的下层。
etc., using the systemctl,
that's a lower layer of services.
请考虑 IP 表与 UFW之间的差异 ( 非复杂防火墙) 。
Think of the difference between IP tables
and the UFW, the uncomplicated firewall.
这就是服务和系统的等价。
That's the equivalent of services and
systemctl.
语法比较详细，但它为您提供了更精细的纹理控制。
The syntax is a bit more verbose, but
it gives you a bit finer grain control.
所以如果你看到你只是想，那跟服务一样，
So if you ever see that you just think,
it's the same thing as service,
就更改了点
just a little bit more modified.
如果您想使用 Node Setup 来运行 Redis ，我使用 Node Redis，
And if you wanna run Redis with
your Node setup, I used Node Redis,
我在工作上用的
I use it at work.
它是与 Redis 交互的一个很好的图书馆。
It's a pretty good library for
interfacing with Redis.
MySQL 相同。
Same thing for MySQL.
如果要安装该安装，那么 sudo 适合安装 mysql-server。
If you wanna install that,
sudo apt install mysql-server.
然后，运行 setup mysql_secure_installation 和
Then you run setup
mysql_secure_installation and
它会通过一些 sane 缺省值运行。
it'll run you through some sane defaults.
如果你想用你的节点，你可以使用非常好的 mysqljs 。
And if you wanna use that with your Node
you can use mysqljs which is pretty good.
它运作良好。
It works well.